<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoupleMatch</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">615536963514690</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb615536963514690</string>
    <string name="facebook_client_token">56789</string>
    <string name="api_key">AIzaSyA9VGT7YIV4nmyMIwa6RHoSKch_-FY8kO0</string>

    <string name="shahabad_matrimony_opc_pvt_ltd_couplematch_in_is_an_matrimonial_platform_with_the_mission_of_providing_high_quality_matrimonial_services_free_of_cost_to_marriage_seekers_this_online_marriage_site_has_been_developed_promoted_and_maintained_by_shahabad_matrimony_opc_private_limited_with_its_registered_office_currently_located_at_shahabad_matrimony_opc_pvt_ltd_sco_27_committee_chowk_shahabad_markanda_distt_kurukshetra_haryana_india_pincode_136135_couplematch_in_is_a_matchmaking_platform_devoted_to_helping_men_and_women_discover_their_soul_mates_if_you_are_seeking_a_bride_or_groom_in_a_specific_community_you_have_reached_the_right_matrimonial_portal_couplematch_in_has_eligible_singles_from_2361_communities_from_all_over_world_to_help_you_find_the_best_matches_this_is_one_stop_matrimonial_website_to_find_brides_and_grooms_without_any_payment_gateway_couplematch_is_also_a_great_platform_for_marriage_seekers_who_have_specific_preferences_about_their_life_partner_you_can_search_a_bride_and_groom_by_location_religion_caste_city_education_hobbies_and_many_such_preferences_registration_membership_and_other_activities_for_free_to_get_access_to_unlimited_brides_and_grooms_choose_your_life_partner_from_many_of_matrimonial_profiles_of_eligible_singles_couplematch_in_is_also_the_first_online_matrimony_website_to_introduce_registration_and_memberships_free_of_cost_you_can_opt_for_personal_assistance_for_matrimony_services_such_as_contacting_interested_profiles_on_your_behalf_for_a_reasonable_fee_of_51000_inr_you_can_generate_horoscope_check_horoscope_compatibility_and_highlight_your_profile_on_couplematch_in_at_couplematch_we_give_top_priority_to_the_security_of_your_profile_we_will_send_you_daily_amp_weekly_match_alerts_to_ensure_that_you_don_t_miss_a_match_couplematch_in_has_a_quick_registration_process_unlike_other_matrimonial_sites_we_are_here_to_help_you_if_you_have_special_requirements_or_specific_preferences_for_your_life_partner_take_a_look_around_and_sign_up_on_our_platform_to_find_a_perfect_bride_or_groom_for_yourself_or_your_loved_ones_email_us_couplematch_in_gmail_com_if_you_have_an_issue_or_sign_up_here_to_begin_your_partner_search"><![CDATA[Shahabad Matrimony (OPC) Pvt Ltd (couplematch.in) is an matrimonial platform with the mission of providing high quality matrimonial services free of cost to marriage seekers. This online marriage site has been developed,promoted and maintained by Shahabad Matrimony (OPC) Private Limited with its registered office currently located at Shahabad Matrimony (OPC) Pvt Ltd , Sco - 27, Committee chowk, Shahabad Markanda, Distt. Kurukshetra, Haryana, India-Pincode:136135. Couplematch.in is a matchmaking platform devoted to helping men and women discover their soul mates. If you are seeking a bride or groom in a specific community, you have reached the right matrimonial portal. Couplematch.in has eligible singles from 2361 communities from all over World to help you find the best matches. This is one stop matrimonial website to find brides and grooms without any payment gateway. Couplematch is also a great platform for marriage seekers who have specific preferences about their life partner. You can search a bride and groom by location,religion, caste, city, education, hobbies and many such preferences. Registration, Membership and Other activities for free to get access to unlimited brides and grooms. Choose your life partner from many of matrimonial profiles of eligible singles. Couplematch.in is also the first online matrimony website to introduce Registration and memberships free of cost. You can opt for personal assistance for matrimony services such as contacting interested profiles on your behalf, for a reasonable fee of 51000/- (INR). You can generate horoscope, check horoscope compatibility and highlight your profile on couplematch.in. At Couplematch, we give top priority to the security of your profile. We will send you daily & weekly match alerts to ensure that you don\'t miss a match. Couplematch.in has a quick registration process unlike other matrimonial sites. We are here to help you if you have special requirements or specific preferences for your life partner. Take a look around and sign-up on our platform to find a perfect bride or groom for yourself or your loved ones. Email us couplematch.in@gmail.com if you have an issue or sign-up here to begin your partner search.]]></string>

    <string-array name="Father_occupation">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Private Job</item>
        <item>Retired</item>
        <item>Govt. Job</item>
        <item>Business</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Mother_occupation">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Private Job</item>
        <item>Retired</item>
        <item>Govt. Job</item>
        <item>Business</item>
        <item>Housewife</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
